6, 20, 25.
Much to approve.
Excuse me.
Please.
To the back.
To the United States of America.
And to the very public for which it stands.
One nation.
And a guy in the middle of the community.
And justice for all.
And to discussion of possible action.
Contract with the drug for John Rogers for the purposes of payment.
For professional quality, documentary and promotional videos.
So this is the few weeks ago to mayor and print a crow in Tyler Tantany.
Mr. Rogers and here in the gallery proposed to do a professional documentary of the
4th of the town regarding the flooding in GRVAM.
What's been done to us in the United States of the United States of the United States of the United States of the United States of the United States of the United States of the United States.
And I get on to a national network like Netflix or whatever.
But Netflix requires a certain quality of camera that he doesn't have.
So in their discussions.
The mayor and Tyler and Trim have found out that $6,700 with all that it would cost.
To buy this camera with a Sony FX3 to produce professional quality.
So contract that I have done.
What co-poses that the city would pay for over $6,700.
And contingent upon that payment he is to purchase a Sony FX3 video camera for purposes of doing the documentary for promotional videos for the city.
A professional quality he would assist us with trying to get Netflix to pick up the documentary.
And at the end of that work the camera would be his free of any grat, how to work in terms of the city.
I talked to when I had a documentary done about one of my cases and so I talked to my agent who was to work with me on that documentary.
And it says $6,700 would be a fair price for that kind of work.
The full promotional videos of the documentary and you said it would be more than fair.
So that's so this is the contract that I prepared for that.
And the reason that we did especially in the mayor called me.
If this was originally from the city on 920.
the mayor earlier this week. He brought up a good point that with the settlements, the
lawsuit settlements, there could possibly be in the A's where they are not allowed to talk
about the settlement or the case at all, so if saying not's grocery, if they were to sign
their settlement with an NDA, they wouldn't be able to participate in the document.
And this way, John, go ahead and hit the ground run and go ahead and get some of that
information beforehand and have it before they sign it. So not just can't be with it if they don't
sign it, if they don't sign their settlement, because that would just end.
It's common when you sign a civil settlement agreement to have a non-disclosure agreement
contained within that, so they wouldn't be able to talk about the case or the things that
had happened to them or the amount, several things they would not be allowed to talk about,
and so that would probably preclude them to a man who would participate if we'd get to the
new beforehand. If we could be right, they haven't signed anything yet.
So if we go ahead and, okay, now then, that's the plan.
That's to be sure and get there.
So our next meeting, one is good, so I think the 20th.
And there's supposed to be before the end, and that's why we have the special meeting, so he started
with some of that. Yeah, I've been there twice, I think, done something to be wrong.
And he does. That's true.
Order of sandwich for me.
This is for tax.
And this camera will only be used for this purpose until, once this is done, then you can, you have all
right to the camera. But I guess my concern is the potential conflict of interest for myself
and even voting on the matter.
If you use it for anything bump-off related during this time, that could, that could look for
what's that on?
I think you're looking at this backwards. We're paying him a payment, and he's going out and purchasing
something on his own. So I think the use of this camera is irrelevant in the respect that he's
not thinking about.
He's a person he purposes until it's finalized, right?
And I think your concern is John Wart from Guelbaugh.
Nice. And his family is on the border for the Guelbaugh, so I got you to ask.
And I don't want anybody to assume that me-
You know, we're partial because, you know, voting whatever, because it's like, this is good for me.
I don't think that that's, you know, because that's really, I mean, like, so I do a lot of video on the work.
But there's something like that.
I didn't voice the view about what I was listening to.
And I like it.
Yeah.
And that's a little bit too, it's like, I can't guarantee you that this gets on there.
I can't.
Sure.
What?
I can guarantee you that you will have at the end of this documentary.
But I'm, I already caught her case and they're getting registered.
Yeah.
We're hour.
The other is, we see you.
And that's the political.
Yeah.
And we're alright, so, all the footage.
We have all the right to all of that.
And you sell it.
It's your money.
If it makes it to that place in the city.
But so, you're still writing for some more.
And we have to make certain scores.
You just write and that will be to be,
I acknowledge, as the producer of director.
Yeah.
I will see it here.
I would like to show this at film festivals
and that's how you get it.
They go to be some of that.
And I'd like to have that in there that we can keep going.
I mean, we would have to call or write,
and if we see you and letting it go,
then we want to do that.
Right.
That should not happen.
So that's what we're doing.
My thoughts are,
67 $1.
And then, basically, just for the documentary,
and then we're just saying,
okay, you can have this personally
for whatever use after that.
Can the sitting up purchase it
so that we can use it in the future for other.
You know,
what if the camera has it?
We have crystal here.
And I asked her if we should purchase the camera
and then do the deal.
Do the deal where he would end up with the camera.
And she said,
no, because then I have to put it in the asset management.
The goal is for him to have the camera
as payment for the videos.
Such.
Okay.
But the easier way is to pay him the cost of the camera
and give him the money with the contingency
that he suspended the money on that camera.
And then use the camera for our purposes.
And at the end of that,
or it doesn't specifically say it in the contract
but at the end, it would be his camera.
But that's what the intent.
That's the intention.
That's why he's taking the money.
Okay.
Thank you.
a little pain, but he's taking care of it and he's taking care of it and he's taking care of it and he's taking care of it
that's why I think we're paying him some money and he's going to go to the military
we assume he's going to do what we want him to do
but I'm doing this not up, not looking for money
no, I'm sorry that I came across that way
I was just thinking why not us purchase it and then we could use it for future events
or whatever it is that we needed to start it out
but I got you
we probably don't have anybody qualified to use the camera
you weren't?
what did you say?
thought
and I'm not there about that this is a 700-year-old
yes
more than fair to the amount
and the money would come out of the money that we set aside every year for a flood
you know, if she would
okay
how much of the length of your $880,000
all the extra that's worth of work in
did that change the July anyway right?
we'll get another 750
and the attorneys have turned everything in so far
so far what you know we have to deal on Friday
which will be expensive
okay
that's really only too much
I'll make a motion to approve
oh second
hi
that is to approve the actual payment
the reading approved contract payment
to be job drivers to provide professional quality documentary
and promotional videos
that was approved
second
hi
and number four
motion
second
hi
thank you guys
I appreciate everybody for